A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, Press Releases, Series 13 FA382
Rockefeller Archive Center
- September 29, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 214)
  Washington, DC, Transcript at Federal City Council Meeting
- September 29, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 215)
  Washington, DC, Remarks and Press Releases at Federal City Council Meeting
- September 29, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 216)
- October 2, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 217)
  Washington, DC, Remarks at Energy Conference Lunch
- October 2, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 218)
  Portland, Oregon, Remarks at Hilton Hotel
- October 3, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 219)
  Portland, Oregon, Remarks at Luncheon for Publishers
- October 3, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 220)
  Portland, Oregon, Remarks at Republican Conference Dinner
- October 6, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 221)
  Washington, DC, Remarks at Energy Conference
- October 6, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 222)
- October 7, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 223)
  Kings Mountain, North Carolina, Remarks at Joe Gamble Stadium
- October 7, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 224)
  Washington, DC, White House Press Release - Vice Presidential Seal -- by President Ford
- November 2, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 225)
  New York City, New York, Remarks on Issues and Answers
- November 3, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 226)
  Washington, DC, Withdrawal Announcement From 1976 Presidential/Vice Presidential Ticket
- November 5, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 227)
  Washington, DC, Address by VP to Staff
- November 6, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 228)
  Washington, DC, Remarks before US Chamber of Commerce Group
- November 6, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 229)
  Washington, DC, Press Conference Regarding Withdrawal decision
- November 10, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 230)
  En route to Austin Texas, aboard Air Force II Press Conference of Vice President
- November 10, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 231)
  Austin, Texas, Remarks at Conference of Women in Public Life
- November 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 232)
  Austin, Texas, Remarks in Tiffany Ballroom
- November 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 233)
- November 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 234)
- November 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 235)
  Austin, Texas, Remarks TV Taping, Capital Eye Program
- November 14, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 236)
  Kansas City, Missouri, Remarks at Future Farmers of American group
- November 14, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 237)
  Kansas City, Missouri, Remarks at Kansas City Auditorium
- November 14, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 238)
  Kansas City, Missouri, Remarks of VP at Signal Hall
- November 14, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 239)
  Lincolnshire, Illinois, Remarks at Lincolnshire Marriot
- November 14, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 240)
  Lincolnshire, Illinois, Remarks at McClory Testimony Dinner
- November 14, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 241)
- November 15, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 242)
  Minneapolis, Minnesota, TV Taping at Registry Hotel
- November 15, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 243)
- November 15, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 244)
  Minneapolis, Minnesota, Remarks at Metropolitan Club Lunch
- November 15, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 245)
  Minneapolis, Minnesota, Q & A at Minn. Metro Club
- November 15, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 246)
  St. Cloud, Minnesota, Remarks at Minnesota Republican State Convention
- November 15, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 247)
  St. Cloud, Minnesota, Remarks at Bicentennial Promotion Center
- November 15, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 248)
  St. Cloud, Minnesota, Remarks at Saint Cloud University campus
- November 15, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 249)
  St. Cloud, Minnesota, Remarks at Elephant Club
- November 18, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 250)
  Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Remarks at Public Forum on Domestic Policy
- November 18, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 251)
  Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Remarks at Benjamin Franklin Hotel
- November 19, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 252)
  Washington, DC, Remarks at Fundraiser For Republican Congressman
- November 20, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 253)
  Wichita, Kansas, Press Conference
- November 20, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 254)
  Wichita, Kansas, GOP Reception
- November 21, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 255)
  Wichita, Kansas, remarks at Republican Governors Conference
- November 21, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 256)
  Wichita, Kansas, Q&A at Republican Governors Conference
- November 25, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 257)
  Indianapolis, Indiana, Transcript, Public Forum on Domestic Policy
- December 3, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 258)
  New York City, Statement before Moreland Commission
- December 4, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 259)
  Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, remarks at Hilton Hotel
- December 4, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 260)
  Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, remarks at Republican Awards Dinner
- December 5, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 261)
  New York City, Remarks at National Association of Manufacturers
- December 9, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 262)
  Los Angeles, California, Remarks at Public Forum
- December 9, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 263)
  Los Angeles, California, TV Taping
- December 10, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 264)
  Washington, DC, Mayflower Hotel, Remarks of VP at Council on Environmental Quality
- December 10, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 265)
  Washington, DC, Remarks at National Center for Productivity and Quality of Working Life
- December 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 266)
  Houston, Texas, Remarks at Black Republican Leadership
- December 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 267)
- December 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 268)
  Houston, Texas, Remarks at Houston Business and Professional Mens Club Dinner
- December 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 269)
  Nashville, Tennessee, remarks at State Committee Lunch
- December 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 270)
  Nashville, Tennessee, Press Conference at Metro Center
- December 12, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 271)
  Houston, Texas, Remarks at Southern Republican Meeting
- December 12, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 272)
  Houston, Texas, Remarks at Hyatt Regency
- December 12, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 273)
  Houston, Texas, TV Taping at Hyatt Regency
- December 17, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 274)
  Washington, DC, Press Conference on Domestic Council
- December 17, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 275)
  Washington, DC, Remarks at President's Safety Award Meeting
- January 14, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 276)
  Washington, DC, Remarks at National Councils of Farmers Cooperatives Shoreham America, Washington, D.C.
- January 19, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 277)
  Washington, DC, Remarks at Opening Session of the 94th Congress
- January 19, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 278)
  Washington, DC, Remarks at Water Quality hearings
- January 20, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 279)
  Statement on conclusion of Water Quality Hearings
- January 26, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 280)
  Remarks to Bolling Air Force Base Wives
- January 26, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 281)
  Salem, West Virginia, Remarks at Salem College
- January 26, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 282)
  Rye, New York, Remarks at Westchester City Republican Committee Dinner
- January 30, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 283)
  Dearborn, Michigan, Press Conference at Hyatt Regency
- January 30, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 284)
  Dearborn, Michigan, Remarks at GOP Reception
- January 30, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 285)
  Dearborn, Michigan, Toast to Governor and Mrs. Milliken, Lovett Hall
- February 2, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 286)
  Remarks at J. Paul Getty Wildlife Conservation Award Ceremony
- February 3, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 287)
  Press Conference in White House Briefing Room
- February 4, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 288)
  Letter to President dated 12/16/75
- February 4, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 289)
  Remarks before Senate Committee on Government Operations
- February 6, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 290)
  Washington DC, Twin Bridges, Marriott Hotel, Remarks at National Council of Arts
- February 6, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 291)
  Washington DC, Twin Bridges, Marriott Hotel, Excerpts of remarks at North East Republican Leadership Lunch
- February 6, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 292)
  Washington DC, Twin Bridges, Marriott Hotel, Introduction of President Ford at North East Republican Leadership Lunch
- February 10, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 293)
  Washington DC, Remarks at Atomic Industry Forum
- February 12, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 294)
  Louisville, Kentucky, Remarks at GOP Committee Meeting
- February 12, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 295)
  Louisville, Kentucky, Remarks at GOP Lincoln Dinner
- February 12, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 296)
  Louisville, Kentucky, TV Taping, Galt House
- February 12, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 297)
  Louisville, Kentucky, Press Conference
- February 14, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 298)
  New York City, Waldorf Astoria, Remarks at Lincoln Day Dinner
- February 19, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 299)
  Washington, DC, Remarks at National Press Club Lunch
- February 20, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 300)
  Lansing, Michigan, Remarks to Michigan State Republican Committee Bicentennial Dinner
- February 20, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 301)
  Lansing, Michigan, Press Conference at Holiday Inn
- February 23, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 302)
  Boston, Massachusetts, Remarks at American Association for Advancement of Science
- February 24, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 303)
  Washington, DC, Statler Hilton, Remarks at National Governors Conference
- February 25, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 304)
  Remarks at swearing-in of Arthur Fletcher, EOB
- February 25, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 305)
  Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Remarks at Bicentennial Bishops and Connectional Church Council Banquet
- March 4, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 306)
  Washington, DC, Interview with Richard Kershaw, BBC
- March 4, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 307)
  Washington, DC, Interview with Martin Diamond
- March 9, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 308)
  New York City, Remarks at Religion in American Life
- March 10, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 309)
  Washington, DC, Jeff McMullen Interview / Australian Broadcasting Comm/Pre Trip Interview
- March 10, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 310)
  National Industry Energy Council Department Of Commerce Pre-Trip Interview
- March 12, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 311)
  Albuquerque, New Mexico, Remarks at GOP Lincoln Day Dinner
- March 12, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 312)
  Albuquerque, New Mexico, Press conference
- March 16, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 313)
  Chicago, Illinois, Remarks at National Association of Wholesale Grocers
- March 17, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 314)
  Chicago, Illinois, Press Conference in Crystal Room
- March 17, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 315)
  Chicago, Illinois, Remarks to Executive Club
- March 17, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 316)
  Washington, DC, Remarks at Joint Economic Committee of Congress
- March 18, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 317)
- March 19, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 318)
  Remarks on Right of Privacy, Domestic Council
- March 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 319)
  Paris, France, Press Conference at American Embassy
- March 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 320)
  Paris, France, Bicentennial Address
- March 29, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 321)
  Singapore, Toast by Vice President at Banquet
- March 29, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 322)
  Singapore, Remarks to American Business Leaders' Reception
- March 30, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 323)
  Canberra, Australia, Lake side Hotel, Press Conference
- April 1, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 324)
  Sydney, Australia, Bicentennial Address, Wentworth Hotel
- April 2, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 325)
  Wellington, New Zealand, Remarks at New Zealand State Luncheon
- April 3, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 326)
  Wellington, New Zealand, Press Conference
- April 7, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 327)
  Reston, Virginia, Remarks to National Energy Leadership Conference
- April 8, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 328)
  Arlington, Virginia, WETZ-TV taping with Robert McNeil Report
- April 12, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 329)
  Statement to Senate Committee re: S.2532, bill for Energy Independence Authority
- April 12, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 330)
  Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Remarks at President Ford Committee Reception Urban Club
- April 12, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 331)
  Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Remarks to Club of Rome
- April 14, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 332)
  Des Moines, Iowa, Press Conference
- April 14, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 333)
  Des Moines, Iowa, Remarks to Republican Dinner
- April 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 334)
  Des Moines, Iowa, WHO-TV taping, Hotel Fort Des Moines
- April 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 335)
- April 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 336)
  Atlanta, Georgia, Remarks at HGOP Fundraising Reception, Peachtree Hotel
- April 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 337)
  Atlanta, Georgia, Press Conference at Peachtree Plaza
- April 18, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 338)
  Interview on "60 Minutes"
- April 20, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 339)
  Washington, DC, Kennedy Center Remarks at President's Commission on Personnel Interchange Dinner
- April 24, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 340)
  Exchange of telegrams by NAR and Senator Jackson
- April 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 341)
  Senator Jackson Reply to telegram
- April 29, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 342)
  Washington, DC Remarks at National Leadership Conference
- April 28, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 343)
  Washington DC, Remarks at Annual Neptune Award Dinner
- April 30, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 344)
  Remarks at George Washington Inaugural Ceremony, Washington Monument
- May 2, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 345)
  Interview on "Issues and Answers," ABC
- May 4, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 346)
  San Francisco, California, Press conference at Fairmont Hotel
- May 4, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 347)
  San Francisco, California, Remarks to Commonwealth Club Lunch
- May 5, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 348)
  Los Angeles California, Press Conference at Biltmore Hotel
- May 7, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 349)
  Astoria, Queens, Remarks at Queens County Republican Dinner
- May 10, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 350)
  Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Remarks to International Press Institute
- May 10, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 351)
  Interview with German television Network, ARD
- May 11, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 352)
  New York City, New York, Remarks at Accion International Dinner
- May 13, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 353)
  Berlin, Germany, Arrival Statement
- May 13, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 354)
  Italy, Udine Airport, Departure Statement
- May 13, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 355)
  Italy, Udine Airport, Arrival Statement
- May 14, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 356)
  Berlin, Germany, Remarks at Luncheon, Schloss Charlott
- May 14, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 357)
  Berlin, Germany, Remarks at U.S. Mission Headquarters
- May 14, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 358)
  Frankfurt, Germany, Arrival Statement, Am Main
- May 14, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 359)
  Berlin, Germany, Departure Statement
- May 14, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 360)
  Frankfurt, Germany, Remarks at Reception at City Hall
- May 14, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 361)
  Frankfurt, Germany, Remarks at Frankfurt City Hall
- May 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 362)
  Frankfurt, Germany, Remarks at Glass Exhibition
- May 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 363)
  Frankfurt, Germany, Departure Statement
- May 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 364)
  Frankfurt, Germany, Toast, Schloss Kronberg Lunch
- May 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 365)
- May 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 366)
- May 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 367)
  Frankfurt, Germany, Texts of Remarks at Frankfurt Am Main at Paulskirche
- May 17, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 368)
  Exchange of remarks between President, VP and Daniel Parker in Oval Office
- May 19, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 369)
  Yorktown, New York, Remarks at Bicentennial Ceremony
- May 20, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 370)
  Cincinnati, Ohio, Remarks at PFC Committee Dinner, Quenn City Club
- May 23, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 371)
  Newport, Rhode Island, Remarks at 50th Anniversary of the Synagogue Council of America
- May 30, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 372)
  New York City, New York, Transcript of Face the Nation
- June 2, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 373)
  Colorado Springs, Colorado, Remarks at Air Force Academy
- June 2, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 374)
  Colorado Springs, Colorado, Press Conference
- June 3, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 375)
  Office of VP, Immediate Release RE: Reagan/Rhodesia
- June 4, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 376)
  Ocean City, Maryland, Maryland State Republican Dinner
- June 4, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 377)
- June 9, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 378)
  Washington, DC, Remarks at National Editorial Association
- June 16, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 379)
  Washington, DC, Remarks at National Housing Conference
- June 16, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 380)
  Washington, DC, Dedication of Old Senate Chamber
- June 17, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 381)
  New York City, New York, Republican State Committee Meeting
- June 17, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 382)
  New York City, New York State, Republic Dinner
- June 18, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 383)
  Greensboro, North Carolina, Remarks at Four Seasons Holiday Inn
- June 18, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 384)
  Greensboro, North Carolina, Republican State Dinner
- June 18, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 385)
  Greensboro, North Carolina, GOP Reception
- June 21, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 386)
  West Orange, New Jersey, Remarks at Town and Campus
- June 21, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 387)
  West Orange, New Jersey, Pre-Convention Dinner Remarks
- June 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 388)
  Washington, DC, Annual Friends of Hebrew University Luncheon
- June 24, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 389)
  Huappauge, New York, Nassau County Republican Dinner
- June 24, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 390)
  Huappauge, New York, press conference Nassau Co. Republican Dinner
- June 30, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 391)
  Washington, DC, Remarks at Congressman Paul Findlely Award Luncheon in the Capitol
- July 1, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 392)
  Washington, DC, Remarks at Chartbook Ceremony and Anniversary of UNIVAC/Census
- July 2, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 393)
  National Archives Documents Ceremony - National Archives, Remarks by VP
- July 4, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 394)
  Washington, DC, Pageant of Freedom
- July 18, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 395)
  Washington, DC, Toast to Queen Elizabeth at Congressional Luncheon
- July 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 396)
  Washington, DC, Inaugural Ceremony of the Albert Einstein Spacearium at the Smithsonian Institution
- July 19, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 397)
  Claymont, Delaware, Victory Kickoff Dinner
- July 19, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 398)
  Wilmington, Delaware, Press Conference at Dupont Hotel
- July 29, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 399)
  Washington, DC, Republican National Hispanic Reception
- August 4, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 400)
  Washington, DC, Toast to President Kekkonen of Finland
- August 4, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 401)
- August 2, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 402)
  Bar Harbor, Maine, Press Conference
- August 2, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 403)
  Seal Harbor, Maine, Boat House Press Conference
- August 9, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 404)
  Kansas City, Missouri, Press Conference
- August 9, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 405)
  Kansas City, Missouri, Platform Committee
- August 9, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 406)
  Kansas City, Missouri, Remarks at Music Hall
- August 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 407)
  Kansas City, Missouri, Meet the Press
- August 16, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 408)
  Kansas City, Missouri, Address Kemper Arena
- August 19, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 409)
  Kansas City, Missouri, Dole Nomination Speech Kemper Arena
- September 14, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 410)
  Washington, DC, Question and Answer on the White House Lawn
- September 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 411)
  Buffalo, New York, Remarks at Reception
- September 16, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 412)
  Buffalo, New York, Press Conference VP and Dole
- September 16, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 413)
  Rochester, New York, Remarks
- September 16, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 414)
  Rochester, New York, Press Conference VP and Dole
- September 16, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 415)
  Syracuse, New York, Remarks
- September 16, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 416)
  Syracuse, New York, Press Conference VP and Dole
- September 16, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 417)
  Binghampton, NY, Remarks
- September 16, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 418)
  Binghampton, NY, Press Conference VP and Dole
- September 16, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 419)
  New York City, New York, Remarks at PFC Headquarters
- September 16, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 420)
  A Press Conference of Rockefeller and Dole NY Tour
- September 16, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 421)
- September 21, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 422)
  Chicago, Illinois, Remarks at Dinner for Jim Thompson
- September 21, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 423)
  Chicago, Illinois, Press Conference
- September 21, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 424)
  Chicago, Illinois, TV Taping
- September 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 425)
  Press Release re: Cleveland, Columbus and Cincinnati
- September 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 426)
  Cleveland, Ohio, Press Conference
- September 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 427)
  Cleveland, Ohio, TV Taping Studio II
- September 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 428)
  Cleveland, Ohio, TV Taping Studio I
- September 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 429)
  Cleveland, Ohio, Remarks at PFC Headquarters
- September 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 430)
  Cleveland, Ohio, Remarks at Breakfast
- September 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 431)
  Cincinnati, Ohio, TV Taping
- September 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 432)
  Cincinnati, Ohio, Remarks at Hamilton Club
- September 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 433)
  Cincinnati, Ohio, Press Conference
- September 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 434)
  Columbus, Ohio, TV Taping
- September 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 435)
- September 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 436)
  Columbus, Ohio, Remarks at Bar Association
- September 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 437)
  Columbus, Ohio, Press Conference
- September 28, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 438)
  Dover, New Jersey, Press Conference
- September 28, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 439)
  Dover, New Jersey, Morris County Republican Fund Raising Luncheon
- September 28, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 440)
  Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Press Conference
- September 28, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 441)
  Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Remarks at Dinner
- September 28, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 442)
  Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Mike Douglas Show Taping
- September 28, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 443)
  Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Interview
- September 28, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 444)
  Hasbrook, New Jersey, Remarks at Candidates' Brunch
- September 29, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 445)
  Remarks at Breakfast at Ciro's, Erie, Pennsylvania
- September 29, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 446)
  Erie, Pennsylvania, Press Conference
- September 29, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 447)
  Erie, Pennsylvania, TV Taping
- September 29, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 448)
  Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, GOP Dinner
- September 29, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 449)
  Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, KRKA TV Taping
- September 29, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 450)
  Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, Luncheon Remarks
- September 29, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 451)
  Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, Press Conference
- September 29, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 452)
  Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, PFC Headquarters, Remarks
- October 4, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 453)
  London, England, McPherson Interview
- October 5, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 454)
  London, England, BBC Interview
- October 5, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 455)
  London, England, Embassy Press Conference
- October 5, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 456)
  London, England, Opening of the North American Indian Art Exhibit
- October 7, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 457)
- October 7, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 458)
- October 7, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 459)
  Chicago, Illinois, Salute to President Dinner
- October 7, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 460)
- October 7, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 461)
  Press Conference, Conrad Hilton Hotel, New York
- October 9, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 462)
  New York, New York, Ukrainian-American Congress Committee Dinner
- October 9, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 463)
  New York City, New York, County Republican Committee Dinner
- October 9, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 464)
  New York City, New York, Columbus Citizens Committee Dinner
- October 12, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 465)
  New York City, New York, Salute to President Dinner
- October 12, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 466)
  New York City, New York, Hilton Hotel, Salute to President Ford Dinner
- October 13, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 467)
  San Francisco, California, Golden Circle Club Luncheon
- October 13, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 468)
  San Francisco, California, Press Conference
- October 13, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 469)
  San Francisco, California, Jim Dunbar Show, KOG-TV
- October 13, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 470)
  Portland, Oregon, Hilton Hotel, Interview with Mike White
- October 13, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 471)
  San Francisco, California, Channel 2 Interview with Connie Chung
- October 13, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 472)
  Sacremento, California, Spencer Michels Interview, KCRA-TV
- October 13, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 473)
  Portland, Oregon, VIP Reception
- October 13, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 474)
  Portland, Oregon, Press Conference
- October 13, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 475)
  Portland, Oregon, Ted Bryant Interview, KOIN-TV
- October 13, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 476)